

Fakhri Hadi **Pridianto**

Content Writer / Digital Marketing

fakhrihadipridianto@gmail.com 🔀

+62 812 9717 9064

Pepelegi Indah Blok F no 4, Waru, Sidoarjo, Indonesia

11 August, 1992 🎹

linkedin.com/in/Fakhri Hadi Pridianto in

instagram.com/@fakhrihp (i)

To bring my strong sense of dedication, motivation, and responsibility to your company, and to utilize my skill qualifications obtained through my college life and real life experience. I am a person who is fairly easy to get along and receptive to criticism and input from the others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Creator YouTube

01/2016 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Making a content (video) about motovlogging.
- Currently have around 22.000 subscribers.

Social Media Officer (Content Writer) Harian SURYA (Tribunnews)

05/2018 - 05/2019

Surabaya, Indonesia

- Achievements/Tasks
- Searching, planning, and writing an article or news and deliver it to the audiences via social media.
- The article must contain several keywords and use SEO writing.

Operational Manager

RESPAWN Bike Wash

Sidoarjo, Indonesia

Achievements/Tasks

05/2019 - 11/2019

Make sure all daily basis activities right on the track.

IT Programmer (Internship)

PT. Telekomunikasi Indonesia

06/2013 - 08/2013

Surabaya, Indonesia

Office Manager

Kantor Notaris Dian Indriastutie, S.H.

11/2019 - Present

EDUCATION

- Achievements/Tasks
- Responsible for keeping an office running smoothly and overseeing administrative support.

O Information Systems

Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology (ITS)

2010 - 2016

SKILLS

Sony Vegas Pro Microsoft Office English Bahasa **Creative Thinking** Effectiveness Productivity Analyzing Issues Lightroom Content Creator Content Writer Social Media

CERTIFICATE

TOEFL (2016)

TOEFL Test ceritification s a requirement for graduation. Score 500/677

Introduction to SAP ERP (2012)

Certification regarding the introduction of SAP with SAP University Alliances

EXPERIENCE

Information System International Conference (10/2015 - 10/2015)

Event Division, hold responsibility as a receptionist to register and directing guests to the venue.

Himpunan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi ITS (06/2011 - 08/2013)

- Internal Affair Department Staff
- Steering Committee

UKM Musik ITS (12/2010 - 09/2011)

- Event Division Staff, plan and organize activities which created by **UKM Musik ITS**

LANGUAGES

English Full Professional Proficiency Bahasa

Native or Bilingual Proficiency